W. R. "Bob" Poage Personal papers, Inclusive: 1766-2008, undated, Bulk: 1937-1978
Baylor University Libraries
- Speeches, 1936-1986, undated; 4
  - Radio Speeches, 1972 March (Box 73, Folder 58)
  - “The Work of Congress and Congressmen,” Delivered in Beverley Hills and Waco, 1972 March 2 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - “Rural Development,” Delivered before Farm Credit Officials, Houston, 1972 March 3 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Speech at Appreciation Dinner, Marlin, 1972 March 3 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Speech at Awards Dinner, Santa Fe Hospital, Temple, 1972 March 7 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1972 April (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Radio Speeches, 1972 April (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - “The Work of Congress and Congressmen”, 1972 April (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Introduction of Dave Hamil to Brazos Electric Cooperative Membership Meeting, Waco, 1972 April 5 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - “The Extended Nutrition Program,” Delivered in Marlin, 1972 April 28 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1972 May (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Radio Speeches, 1972 May (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Statement on San Gabriel to House Subcommittee on Public Works, 1972 May 15 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Speech to Association of Rhodesian Cotton Growers, Salisbury, Rhodesia, 1972 May 23 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1972 June (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Radio Speeches, 1972 June (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Speech to Flue-Cured Tobacco Cooperative Stabilization Corporation, Raleigh, 1972 June 30 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1972 July (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 1972 July (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Radio Speeches, 1972 July (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1972 August (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Radio Speeches, 1972 August (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - “Can We Maintain Our Farm Programs?” Delivered at Corn Products Company, International Executive Seminar, New Jersey, 1972 August 7 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Statement on Watershed Development to House Publics Works Committee, 1972 August 15 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1972 September (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Editorial on Addressing Crime, circa 1972 September (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Press Releases, 1972 October (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1972 October (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Press Release on Increasing Cotton Loan Rate, 1972 October 16 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - “The Cotton Price Situation,” Delivered to National Farmers Union, 1972 October 18 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Remarks to Little River-San Gabriel Soil & Water Conservation District, Bartlett, Texas, 1972 November 6 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - News Release on Travel to Bangladesh, 1972 November 14 (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - “The Rural Development Act,” Delivered to Agricultural and Community Banker Division, American Bankers Association, Denver, 1972 November 14 (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - “The Cotton Situation and What We Can Do About It,” Delivered to Cotton Producers Association, Lubbock, 1972 November 15 (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - Press Releases, 1972 December (Box 74, Folder 34)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1973 January (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - Press Releases, 1973 January (Box 74, Folder 36)
  - Radio Speech on R.E.A. Loans, 1973 January 4 (Box 74, Folder 37)
  - Address to National Wool Growers Association Convention, Washington, D.C., 1973 January 23 (Box 74, Folder 38)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1973 February (Box 74, Folder 39)
  - Press Releases, 1973 February (Box 74, Folder 40)
  - Address to Ranch Credit School for Commercial Bankers, College Station, 1973 February 13 (Box 74, Folder 41)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1973 March (Box 74, Folder 42)
  - Press Release on Responding to Food Price Concerns, 1973 March 20 (Box 74, Folder 43)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1973 April (Box 74, Folder 44)
  - “Yale Story,” Delivered to South Carolina Textile Manufacturers Association Meeting, Charleston, 1973 April 13 (Box 74, Folder 45)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1973 May (Box 74, Folder 46)
  - Press Releases, 1973 May (Box 74, Folder 47)
  - Statement to Select Committee on Committees, 1973 May 4 (Box 74, Folder 48)
  - Commencement Address to University of Mary-Hardin Baylor, Belton, 1973 May 19 (Box 74, Folder 49)
  - Press Releases, 1973 June (Box 74, Folder 50)
  - Remarks at Dedication of Farm Bureau Building, Waco, 1973 June 13 (Box 74, Folder 51)
  - “Agricultural, Environmental and Consumers Protection Appropriation, 1974”, 1973 June 15 (Box 74, Folder 52)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1973 July (Box 74, Folder 53)
  - Press Releases, 1973 July (Box 74, Folder 54)
  - Press Releases, 1973 August (Box 74, Folder 55)
  - “Agriculture and Consumer Protection Act of 1973,” “Congressional Record”, 1973 August 3 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Address to the Waco Downtown Lions Club, 1973 August 22 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1973 September (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, 1973 September (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Remarks of Olin E. Teague, 1973 September 17 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 1973 October (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Veteran’s Day Speeches, Waco, 1973 October 22 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Speech at Governor’s Conference on Rural Development, 1973 October 23 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - “Destruction of Peanut Program in an Unwise Act,” “Congressional Record”, 1973 October 29 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1973 November (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - “Our Sugar Program - A Part of Our Farm Program,” Delivered at Santa Rosa, Texas, 1973 November 11 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - “Remarks on Robert Ewing Thompson,” “Congressional Record”, 1973 November 15 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1973 December (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Speech Before Waco Rotary Club, 1973 December 31 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - “Should Congress Eliminate Farm Subsidy Payments?”, “American Legion Magazine”, 1974 January (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - “The Energy Problem - Long Term,” Delivered to Northwest Kiwanis Club, Waco, 1974 January 2 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - “Energy Problem — Immediate Crisis,” Delivered to Eastside Rotary Club, 1974 January 4 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - “The Energy Crisis (Impeachment),” Delivered to Brownwood Rotary Club, 1974 January 9 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Commemorating First Troy Rural Development Community Facilities Loan, 1974 January 14 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Re-Election Announcements, 1974 January 17 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - “Remarks on Harold Dunbar Cooley,” “Congressional Record”, 1974 January 28 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Press Release on Military Academy Nominations, 1974 February 4 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - “The R.E.A. Act of 1973,” Delivered at National Rural Electric Cooperative Association Convention, San Francisco, 1974 February 11 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Speech at National Association of Conservation Districts Convention, Houston, 1974 February 12 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - “Naming Civilian Conservation Corps Center and Cross Timbers National Grasslands in Honor of Late President Lyndon B. Johnson,” “Congressional Record”, 1974 March 21 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - “Befuddled and Confused Story,” Delivered in Saint Joseph, Missouri, 1974 March 29 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - “Befuddled and Confused Story,” Delivered at Exchange Club Golden Deeds Banquet, Copperas Cove, Texas, 1974 March 30 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - “Befuddled and Confused Story”, 1974 April (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1974 April (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Statements to House Appropriations Committee, 1974 April 23 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Press Releases, 1974 May (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - “National School Lunch Act Amendments,” “Congressional Record”, 1974 May 7 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Statement to Subcommittee on Library and Memorials, 1974 May 9 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - “The Relation Between Farm Prices and Production,” Delivered at Corn Products Company, International Headquarters, New Jersey, 1974 May 13 (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1974 June (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Dedication of Cameron Mall, 1974 June 7 (Box 75, Folder 36)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1974 July (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - Statement to House Rules Committee, 1974 July 10 (Box 75, Folder 38)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1974 August (Box 75, Folder 39)
  - Statement to Livestock and Grains Subcommittee, 1974 August 6 (Box 75, Folder 40)
  - Statement on President Richard Nixon’s Resignation, 1974 August 8 (Box 75, Folder 41)
  - “Let’s Maintain a Reasonable Balance,” “San Angelo Standard Times” Editorial, 1974 August 15 (Box 75, Folder 42)
  - “Inflation,” Delivered at Food and Agriculture Economic Summit Conference on Inflation, Chicago, 1974 September 12-13 (Box 75, Folder 43)
  - Statement to Committee on Public Works, 1974 September 24 (Box 75, Folder 44)
  - “Congressional Record” and Statements, 1974 October (Box 75, Folder 45)
  - Speech to 77th Annual Convention of U.S.D. Independent Phone Association, San Francisco, 1974 October 7 (Box 75, Folder 46)
  - Speech to Annual Meeting of Southern Agricultural Chemicals Association, Pine Mountain, Georgia, 1974 October 28 (Box 75, Folder 47)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1974 December (Box 75, Folder 48)
  - Speech Honoring Earl L. Butz, Chicago, 1974 December 1 (Box 75, Folder 49)
  - “Some Aspects of Inflation,” Delivered to Waco Rotary Club, 1974 December 30 (Box 75, Folder 50)
  - “Some Aspects of Inflation”, 1975 January (Box 75, Folder 51)
  - Statements, 1975 January (Box 75, Folder 52)
  - Speech to United States Beet Sugar Association, Santa Barbara, California, 1975 January 7 (Box 75, Folder 53)
  - Dedication of New King’s Daughters Hospital, Temple, 1975 January 25 (Box 75, Folder 54)
  - Statement on Unused Campaign Funds, 1975 March 7 (Box 75, Folder 55)
  - “Frank Mayborn,” Delivered at Central Texas College, Killeen, 1975 April 18 (Box 75, Folder 56)
  - Unveiling of Statue by Brazos Electric Co-Op, Waco, 1975 April 28 (Box 75, Folder 57)
  - “Veto of the Emergency Agricultural Act of 1975,” “Congressional Record”, 1975 May 13 (Box 75, Folder 58)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1975 June (Box 75, Folder 59)
  - Introduction of Lloyd Bentsen at Waco Democratic Rally, 1975 June 7 (Box 75, Folder 60)
  - Speech to Waco Kiwanis Club, 1975 July 1 (Box 75, Folder 61)
  - Radio Recording on Namar Media Group, 1975 August 16-17 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - “Energy Conservation and Crude Oil Policy Act of 1975,” “Congressional Record”, 1975 September 17 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - “Beef Research and Information Act,” “Congressional Record”, 1975 October 2 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - “Congress Like School,” Delivered to District High Schools, 1975 November 21-24 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - “Legislative Trends,” Delivered to Waco Rotary Club, 1975 December 29 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1976 January (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Groundbreaking of W. R. Poage Federal Building, Temple, 1976 January 5 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Speech to McGregor Rotary Club, 1976 January 14 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Speech to Burnet Businessmen, 1976 January 15 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Speech to San Saba Chamber of Commerce, 1976 January 15 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Arbor Day Speeches, 1976 January 16 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1976 February (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1976 March (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Press Release on Federal Academies, 1976 March 12 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Speech at Joint Civic Clubs Meeting, Taylor, Texas, 1976 March 26 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1976 April (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1976 April (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Lew Barringer Dinner, 1976 April 7 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Dedication of Poage Drive, Woodway, 1976 April 24 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1976 May (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Statement to House Committee on Post Office and Civil Service, 1976 May 4 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Speech to Burnet Foundation Industrial Company, Burnet, Texas, 1976 May 28 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Remarks at Flag Raising at Powers Chapel Cemetery, 1976 May 30 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Speech at Forage-Grasslands Center, Temple, 1976 May 30 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - “Revenue Sharing,” “Congressional Record”, 1976 June 10 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - July 4th Speech in Belton, 1976 July 4 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Speech Delivered to Northwest Kiwanis Club, Waco, 1976 July 7 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Speech at Groundbreaking of Coleman Flood Prevention Structure, 1976 July 12 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Speech to Texas Sheep and Goat Raisers Association, San Angelo, 1976 July 17 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Press Release on Elements of Federal Farm Program, 1976 July 23 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - “Congressional Record” and Press Release, 1976 August (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1976 September (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - Press Releases, 1976 September (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - Statement to Subcommittee on International Development Institutions and Finance, 1976 September 15 (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - Speech to Lions, Rotary and Kiwanis Clubs of Lampasas, 1976 October 6 (Box 76, Folder 35)
  - Speech at Milam County Appreciation Dinner, Rockdale, Texas, 1976 October 7 (Box 76, Folder 36)
  - Speech at Texas A&M Brush Control Field Day, Guthrie, Texas, 1976 October 7 (Box 76, Folder 37)
  - Speech to Clifton Lions Club, 1976 October 12 (Box 76, Folder 38)
  - “The Work of Congress and Congressmen,” Delivered to Richfield High School, Waco, 1976 October 12 (Box 76, Folder 39)
  - Speech at Dedication of W. R. Poage Federal Building, Temple, 1976 October 13 (Box 76, Folder 40)
  - Speech at Little River Award Ceremony, 1976 October 13 (Box 76, Folder 41)
  - Speech at Temple Appreciation Dinner, 1976 October 13 (Box 76, Folder 42)
  - Speech at Baylor Law School, Waco, 1976 October 14 (Box 76, Folder 43)
  - Speech at Copperas Cove Exchange Club, 1976 October 20 (Box 76, Folder 44)
  - Speech to Bellmead Lions Club, 1976 October 211 (Box 76, Folder 45)
  - Speech at Appreciation Dinner, Granbury, Texas, 1976 October 25 (Box 76, Folder 46)
  - Speech at Texas Cattle Feeders Association, Amarillo, 1976 October 26 (Box 76, Folder 47)
  - Appreciation Dinner at Cowhouse Hotel, Killeen, 1976 October 27 (Box 76, Folder 48)
  - Speech to Senior Citizens of Killeen, 1976 October 27 (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Speech at West Texas Chamber of Commerce, Brownwood, 1976 October 29 (Box 76, Folder 50)
  - Press Release on Poage Surgery, 1976 November 13 (Box 76, Folder 51)
  - “Proposed Blanket of Amnesty of Draft Evaders,” “Congressional Record”, 1977 January 11 (Box 76, Folder 52)
  - Press Release on President Jimmy Carter’s Inauguration, 1977 January 20 (Box 76, Folder 53)
  - “A Tribute to Gerald R. Ford,” “Congressional Record”, 1977 February 1 (Box 76, Folder 54)
  - Speech to American National Cattlemen’s Association, Atlanta, 1977 February 1 (Box 76, Folder 55)
  - Statements to House Committees, 1977 March (Box 76, Folder 56)
  - Press Release on Health and Resignation Rumors, 1977 May (Box 76, Folder 57)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1977 July (Box 76, Folder 58)
  - “Forty Years of Farm Legislation”, 1977 July 6 (Box 76, Folder 59)
  - Dedication of Torbett-Hutchings-Smith Clinic, Marlin, 1977 August 13 (Box 76, Folder 60)
  - “Mr. Foley, Chairman of the House Agriculture Committee,” “Congressional Record”, 1977 September 16 (Box 76, Folder 61)
  - Retirement Speech Delivered in Waco, 1977 September 24 (Box 76, Folder 62)
  - “U.S. Wool Industry at a Crossroad,” “Congressional Record”, 1977 October 12 (Box 76, Folder 63)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1977 November (Box 76, Folder 64)
  - Dedication of Grasslands Center, Temple, 1977 November 10 (Box 76, Folder 65)
  - “Democracy - How It Works,” Delivered to American Bankers Association, Kansas City, Missouri, 1977 November 14 (Box 76, Folder 66)
  - “Democracy - How it Works,” Delivered to Waco Rotary Club, 1977 December 12 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Brownwood Appreciation Dinner, 1977 December 15 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Profile of Poage’s Career by L.T. Easley, Fowler West, and Bernard Brenner, circa 1978 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Remarks to Commodity Club, Washington, D.C., 1978 January 18 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - “Should Congressional Terms be Limited to Twelve Years?”, Article for “Family Weekly Magazine”, 1978 January 26 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - “American Agriculture’s Tribute to Bob Poage,” Dawson Mathis, “Congressional Record”, 1978 January 31 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - “Congressional Record” and Press Release, 1978 February (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Statement to Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, 1978 March 14 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Remarks at Dinner in Poage’s Honor, Washington, D.C., 1978 March 14 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Groundbreaking of Congressional Library at Baylor University, Waco, 1978 March 28 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - “Congressional Record” and Press Release, 1978 April (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Statement on Water Project Appropriations, 1978 April 4 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1978 May (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Statement on Agricultural Exports and U.S. Foreign Economic Policy, 1978 May 4 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Opening of Temple Telegram’s New Home, Temple, 1978 May 14 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Press Release on World Bank Aiding Terrorists in Africa, 1978 May 24 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - “Proposed Increase in Beef Imports,” “Congressional Record”, 1978 June 8 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Speech to State Conference of Animal Services, 1978 June 28 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Dedication of New Facilities for Rural Electrification Administration, Washington, D.C., 1978 June 29 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1978 July (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Speech on Central Texas Scenic Parkway, Lampasas, 1978 July 3 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Introduction of Marvin Leath at Campaign Dinner, Waco, 1978 August 22 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Ribbon Cutting Ceremony for High Plains Agribusiness Exposition, Lubbock, 1978 August 25 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1978 September (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Speech Honoring Charles Stenholm, Stephenville, Texas, 1978 September 5 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - “Mr. Sam,” “Congressional Record”, 1978 October 8 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Dedication at E.C. (Took) Gathings Federal Building, Jonesboro, Arkansas, 1978 October 27 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Speech at Appreciation Dinner for Sam Hall, Marshall, Texas, 1978 October 28 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Unused Speech on Natural Resources, circa 1978 December (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Dedication of Granger Dam, 1978 December 1 (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - Speech to Waco Rotary Club, 1978 December 11 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - Speech at Annual Meeting of Limestone Electric Cooperative, Mart, 1979 June 30 (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - “The Constitution Our Fathers Gave Us,” Delivered at Daughters of the American Revolution, Waco, 1979 September 22 (Box 77, Folder 33)
  - Speech at Groundbreaking of Miss Nellie’s Pretty Place, Waco, 1986 March 19 (Box 77, Folder 34)
  - Statement on Additional Funds for Farmers Home Activities, 1968 February 27 (Box 77, Folder 39)
  - Statement of Congressman W. R. Poage on Lawlessness in Chicago, 1968 August 31 (Box 77, Folder 40)
  - "The Rural Electrification Administration and Rural America," Delivered to the House of Representatives, 1971 June 10 (Box 77, Folder 41)
  - Statement of W. R. Poage before the Agriculture-Environmental and Protection Subcommittee of the House Committee on Appropriations, 1972 May 17 (Box 77, Folder 42)
- Travel, 1930-1979, undated; 5
  As a delegate to the Interparliamentary Union and a member of the House Committee on Agriculture, Poage often traveled for agricultural or diplomatic purposes. This series contains many of the documents related to his travels — everything from dossiers to bumper stickers. Several foreign languages are depicted in this subseries including Arabic, English, French, German, Japanese, Korean, Persian, Portuguese, and Spanish. Most of the items in this series are in good condition with a few acidic and fragile items included.
  Postcards
  - Poage Trips, 1944-1979, undated; 1
    This subseries consists mostly of correspondence, itineraries, schedules, official documents, and other personal or governing information related to Representative Poage’s international travels. Languages depicted in this subseries include Arabic, English, French, German, Japanese, Korean, Persian, Portuguese, and Spanish. Overall, the items in this subseries are in good condition.
    - Afghanistan, Public Law 480 Report, 1959 September (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - Africa, Agricultural Reports for House Committee on Agriculture Trip, 1974 September-November (Box 77, Folder 36)
    - Africa, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 37)
    - Africa, Correspondence and Notes on Trip Preparations, 1970 September-October (Box 77, Folder 38)
    - Africa, Correspondence on 1964 Trip, 1964 September-1965 April (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Africa, Correspondence on Agriculture Committee Trip, 1970 October-November (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Africa, Correspondence, Itineraries, and Programs for Trip by Poage and O.C. Fisher, 1958-1959 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Africa, Country Reports for House Agriculture Committee Trip, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Africa, Department of State Telegrams on Trip Preparations, 1970 September-November (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Africa, Expense Memorandum, 1964 November (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Africa, Expenses for Trip with O.C. Fisher, 1958 September (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Africa, Final Preparations for Agricultural Committee Trip, Correspondence, Flight Schedule, Map, and Press Releases, 1970 September-November (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Africa, Itinerary and Correspondence, 1970 November (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Africa, Itineraries, Memorandums, and Correspondence, 1964 October-December (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Africa, Personal Expense Notes, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Africa, Travel Journal, 1958 September-October (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Africa, Travel Journal, 1964 November-December (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Africa, Travel Journal, 1970 November (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Africa, Travel Journal, 1972 May (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Alaska, Travel Journal, 1946 August (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Algeria, Arrival Statement, 1972 November 18 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - America, General Correspondence, 1958-1979 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - America, Schedule, Maps, and Correspondence for Committee Trip to North Central States, 1967 September (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - America, Travel Itinerary, 1963 August-September (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - America, Travel Schedule Drafts for Committee Field Trip to Northeast States, 1967 August (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - American Interparliamentary Conference, 1959 May 10-17 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Antarctica, Briefs and Bulletins, 1962 October (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Antarctica, Bulletin from U.S. Antarctic Projects Officer, 1964 June (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Antarctica, Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Antarctica, Geological Report, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Antarctica, Travel Journal, 1962 November (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Argentina, Itinerary, Staff List, and Sugar Industry Report, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Argentina, Travel Journal, 1969 July-August (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Asia, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Australia, Complete Trip Brief (1 of 2), 1970 April-May (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Australia, Complete Trip Brief (2 of 2), 1970 April-May (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Australia, Correspondence and Itineraries, 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Australia, Correspondence, Schedules, and Timetables, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Australia, Invitations, Itineraries, Tickets, and Briefs, 1970 May (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Australia, Sugar Industry Report, 1970 May (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Australia, Travel Journal, 1970 April-May (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Bahrain, Schedule and Travel List, 1972 November (Box 81, Folder 2)